tystoybox.com 2004-06-05

# PrivacyPolicy

**  P**rivacy ** P**olicy   

We are committed to making your online transaction safe, secure and confidential to the highest standards available.

**Following are some relevant facts about how we treat your information**

**We do not share or sell data.** We collect billing and shipping information in order to process your order and deliver it to its destination. This information is used only by Ty's Toy Box and the couriers we use for the purposes of fulfilling your order . Personal information collected through this site is used only for our internal purposes. We will not sell your personal information, or authorize third parties to use such information for any commercial purpose, without your prior consent. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not automatically collect personal information such as your name, address, telephone number or email address. Such information will be collected only if you provide it to us voluntarily in order to order products, enter a contest or promotion, or sign up to receive our eUpdate newsletter. We don't require that any personal information be provided in order to view our website.

**How we use personal information sent to us by consumers:**

Information collected by Ty's Toy Box is used to:

  * allow you to order products, register for eUpdate and participate in special promotions;
  * improve the site by observing products that are most popular; and
  * personalize the delivery of information and recommend products to you.

Your personal information may also be used to create statistics about tystoybox.com ™ that we use to measure our performance. These statistics do not contain any information that could identify you personally.

Ty's Toy Box does not sell your personal information to any organization for any purpose.  

**We do send email.** We will send you email at regular intervals to ensure that you are always kept up to date on the status of your order. From time to time we send additional eflyers out to inform our customers of specials or promotions that they might be interested in. You can choose not to receive the eflyers by selecting this option in your my Ty's Toy Box account. Or you can send an email to nothanks@tystoybox.com and request to be removed from our list. 

**We offer Optional Registration.** We recommend that you register as a customer in order to take advantage of the many benefits of maintaining an account. Unlike many other sites, registration is not necessary for placing orders. We offer a "buy now" option which only requires the basic information required to process your order Please note that this will limit access to your order history and an address book.. 

**We DO NOT store credit card data.** We do not store your credit card information. Since the banking institutions are the most secure of any site, we have designed our systems so that only our bank's authorized payment provider stores your credit card information. This transaction is handled using the highest level of protection available. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption and is automatically updated with the latest security advancements. 

**Password Protected Accounts.** When you decide to register an account in order to take advantage of the address book, quick pay and order restoration features, your account information is secured by password protection assigned and maintained by you. If you forget your password, this information is only released to your specific email address recorded in your account profile. It is not given out in any other situation without identity verification provided by you. The account information contains the billing and shipping addresses, phone numbers and email address provided and maintained by you as well as your order history. Credit card information is not included in this file. 

**We use Cookies.** Like most advanced sites these days, tystoybox.com ™ uses cookies to make your shopping experience the best it can be. No personal or credit card information is stored in these cookies and there is no risk to your privacy or security caused by this action. It is simply an identifier transferred to your system from ours that helps us manage your transaction. It remembers items in your basket and currency selections. You can choose not to use cookies if you like. We do not require cookies to process your order however the lack of the memory feature may cause some frustration in certain situations.

**Getting Your Consent**

By using tystoybox.com ™ you are consenting to the collection and use of personal and account information by Ty's Toy Box, for the purposes set out in this policy.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

All changes will be posted on tystoybox.com promptly to inform visitors of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
